<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Digital Humanitarian Network</title>
    <link href="https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com" />
    <updated>2019-07-29T10:22:05-04:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>DH Network</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>After Action Reports (Archive)</title>
        <author>
            <name>DH Network</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com/after-action-reports-archive.html"/>
        <id>https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com/after-action-reports-archive.html</id>

        <updated>2019-07-29T10:13:26-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Guidance on Common Operational Datasets (CODs): Report includes compiled resources for future Common Operational Dataset&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <div class="content">
<div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden">
<div class="field-items">
<div class="field-item even">
<div><strong><a href="https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B6HB45QudldEU2xzNlB0YlVxNms/view?usp=sharing">Guidance on Common Operational Datasets (CODs)</a></strong>: Report includes compiled resources for future Common Operational Dataset (CODs) activations.
<p><strong><a href="https://docs.google.com/document/d/1qypMzKiVYOCSA8jr1MiZzpv0eIsV9dbVNXMq6i-6YXg/edit">Hurricane Matthew (Haiti) After Action Report</a></strong>: Report includes review of digital coordination, products and processes used, feedback, and recommendations.</p>
</div>
<div> </div>
<div><strong><a href="https://docs.google.com/document/d/1JGsfEZJ4LT6gFDBfrGRc3sEVE5LkaOihFgjKa_NOCeI/edit?usp=sharing">Libyan 2017 Humanitarian Needs Overview (HNO)</a></strong>: Report highlights the methodology and results from leveraging volunteer capacity for a short-duration Secondary Data Review, including <a href="https://drive.google.com/drive/u/1/folders/0B0pBAbW62rZqYnoxQkJ6bi1yUDg">supporting resources</a>.</div>
<p><a href="https://docs.google.com/document/d/1P4NTwrsrDCWKxRy6ZaAjMcuWgP553Bobmv-W6P1WUN4/edit#heading=h.kg4lr7aislwd"><strong>Ecuador Earthquake After Action Report</strong></a>: This was not a DHN activation, however it was an opportunity to further document best practices in digital response. Report includes background, digital coordination, products &amp; outcomes, as well as recommendations.</p>
<p><strong>After Action report from the Nepal Coordinator</strong>:  This report highlights lessons learned over the past six months while serving as the Digital Humanitarian Coordinator, specifically highlighting recommendations, DHC outcomes, and strengths/weaknesses of current response procedure.</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="http://humanityroad.org/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/Nepal-After-Action-Report1.pdf"><strong>Humanity Road's After Action Report for the Nepal Earthquake</strong></a><strong>:</strong> Humanity Road’s (HR’s) overall disaster response activities began on April 25th and ended on June 12th. In addition to producing general daily situation reports and conducting social media monitoring and amplification, HR was activated for five mission-specific projects.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="http://docs.google.com/document/d/1h3hL6o0YUmJUtUt2Z2hZyN73JCh0UdpS2eW9-TefmRY/edit?usp=sharing"><strong>DHN Activation for Cyclone Pam in Vanuatu After Action Report</strong></a>: The report includes information on the activation, participating DHN members and activities, resulting products with feedback, and lessons learned.   </p>
<p><a href="http://docs.google.com/document/d/1eMWyvWA1XFOEc3F6u1AqJJ7InVLj8VMQyXku2v1LlMY/edit?usp=sharing"><strong>After Action report from the West Africa Ebola DHN Coordinator</strong></a>: This report highlights lessons learned over the past six months while serving as DHN Ebola Coordinator, specifically highlighting experience with extended digital response, health activation, as well as serving as the first full-time remote coordinator.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Data Protection (Archive)</title>
        <author>
            <name>DH Network</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com/data-protection-archive.html"/>
        <id>https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com/data-protection-archive.html</id>

        <updated>2019-07-29T10:10:03-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    As Volunteer and Technical Communities (V&amp;TCs) may process significant amounts of Personally Identifiable Information (PII)&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>As Volunteer and Technical Communities (V&amp;TCs) may process significant amounts of Personally Identifiable Information (PII) as part of their respective contribution to an activation of the Digital Humanitarian Network. Inherent to this is the need to approach personal data with the consideration for people’s privacy. Data protection is especially relevant when it is of a sensitive nature and inadvertent disclosure could result in harm or threat to the safety of those individuals concerned.</p>
<p>Some of the DHN members specifically integrate the principle of minding people’s privacy in their respective Codes of Conduct (e.g. the <a href="http://gwob.org/about/code-of-collaboration/">Geeks Without Bounds Code of Collaboration</a>). As the exploitation of personal data entails a certain degree of responsibility, members of the Digital Humanitarian Networks are highly encouraged to underline the aforementioned principle in their respective Codes and to integrate it in their work processes, for example by agreeing on safeguards regarding data retention and collecting only relevant information. It follows that volunteers should understand and acknowledge their own importance when handling personal data and make enlightened decisions with regard to the degree of accessibility and the channels of communication used for sharing personal data by recognizing such a principle.</p>
<p>While considering the question of data protection, V&amp;TCs may also wish to establish guidelines explicitly shared with the volunteers on the question of liability for members actions explaining how virtual responses can subject digital volunteers to tort liability.</p>
<p>Although no universal set of principles on the matter have been agreed to by the main actors of humanitarian relief, a number of pertinent organizations have developed their own <strong>Standards and Guidelines</strong>:</p>
<ul>
<li>The <a href="http://www.icrc.org/eng/assets/files/other/icrc-002-0999.pdf#page=79">ICRC Professional Standards and Guidelines for Managing Sensitive Protection Information</a> (page 77)</li>
<li>The <a href="http://oecdprivacy.org/">OECD Privacy Principles</a></li>
<li>The <a href="http://publications.iom.int/bookstore/free/IOMdataprotection_web.pdf#page=12">International Organization for Migration Data Protection Principles</a></li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>Further resources on Data Protection and liability:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><a href="http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/data-collection/legal/index_en.htm">Collecting &amp; processing personal data: what is legal? (European Commission)</a></li>
<li><a href="http://csrc.nist.gov/publications/nistpubs/800-122/sp800-122.pdf">Guide to Protecting the Confidentiality of Personally Identifiable Information (National Institute of Standards and Technology)</a></li>
<li><a href="http://www.google.com/url?q=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.wilsoncenter.org%2Farticle%2Fcommons-lab-releases-report-liability-for-digital-volunteers-disasters&amp;sa=D&amp;sntz=1&amp;usg=AFQjCNH-vcLT_KuQ5zbXJmXmb2CCIrRQUg">Responding To Liability: Evaluating and Reducing Tort Liability for Digital Volunteers (Wilson Center's Commons Lab)</a></li>
</ul>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Materials Page temp</title>
        <author>
            <name>DH Network</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com/materials-page-temp.html"/>
        <id>https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com/materials-page-temp.html</id>

        <updated>2019-07-18T13:31:39-04:00</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Code of Conduct (Archive)</title>
        <author>
            <name>DH Network</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com/code-of-conduct.html"/>
        <id>https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com/code-of-conduct.html</id>

        <updated>2019-07-21T14:49:50-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Code of Conduct, often referred to as a Code of Ethics, is a set of&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p dir="ltr">Code of Conduct, often referred to as a Code of Ethics, is a set of rules outlining the responsibilities of or proper practices for an individual, party or organization. A Code of Conduct formalizes a number of acting principles and “minimum” standards: a body publishing its own Code of conduct commits itself to conform to these standards and expects the same from the individuals composing it and representing it.</p>
<p dir="ltr">A number of DHN members have drafted their own Codes, which often overlap in their principles. New and existing DHN members are strongly encouraged to develop their own individual Codes of Conduct which they would abide to and which would apply to their respective pools of volunteers, in the aim of reflecting the ethical values and the professional standards upheld by the DHN as a whole.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Codes produced by existing DHN members :</strong></p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr"><a href="http://gwob.org/about/code-of-collaboration/">GWOB Code of Collaboration</a> (also adopted by the <a href="https://wiki.ushahidi.com/display/WIKI/Code+of+Conduct">Ushahidi community</a>)</p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr"><a href="http://www.giscorps.org/index.php?option=com_content&amp;task=view&amp;id=63&amp;Itemid=70">GISCorps Code of Conduct</a></p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr"><a href="http://community.amstat.org/SWB/CodeofConduct">Statistics without Borders' Code of Conduct</a></p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr"><a href="http://www.humanityroad.org/FAQRetrieve.aspx?ID=49330">Humanity Road's Code of Conduct and Ethics Pledge</a></p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr"><a href="http://www.unv.org/fileadmin/docs/conditions_of_service/COS_INTL_SPEC_20080901_.pdf">United Nations Volunteers Code of Conduct</a></p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://docs.google.com/a/standbytaskforce.com/file/d/0B8j8PoWWdddLRVl0RW9DVDFJSDQ/edit" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Standby Volunteer Task Force's Code of Conduct</a></p>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr">Such codes are suggestive examples of how Codes of Conducts might be formulated and may serve as a starting point for new DHN members to establish their own Code.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Further examples of Codes of Conduct established within international humanitarian response bodies include:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr"><a href="http://www.icrc.org/eng/assets/files/publications/icrc-002-1067.pdf">Code of Conduct for the International Red Cross and Red Crescent Movement and Non-Governmental Organisations in Disaster Relief</a></p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr"><a href="https://www.google.ch/url?sa=t&amp;rct=j&amp;q=&amp;esrc=s&amp;source=web&amp;cd=2&amp;cad=rja&amp;ved=0CDUQFjAB&amp;url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.unicef.org%2Fpathtraining%2FDocuments%2FSession%25204%2520Humanitarian%2520Principles%2FParticipant%2520Manual%2F4.2%2520UNICEF%2520Humanitarian%2520Principles.doc&amp;ei=_DTMUauNNMGr7AaejoBo&amp;usg=AFQjCNG-yqtJ8wBal9kQdb6JpbF1CFYPrA&amp;sig2=xyny_70UXo_FA1jnPQWxow&amp;bvm=bv.48340889,d.ZGU">UNICEF's Humanitarian Principles</a></p>
</li>
<li dir="ltr">
<p dir="ltr"><a href="http://www.un.org/en/ethics/pdf/StandConIntCivSE.pdf">The United Nations standards of conduct for the international civil service</a></p>
</li>
</ul>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Overview (Archive)</title>
        <author>
            <name>DH Network</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com/digital-humanitarian-network-overview-video.html"/>
        <id>https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com/digital-humanitarian-network-overview-video.html</id>

        <updated>2019-07-21T14:50:07-04:00</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/scdb1XFVAyE" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>About DHN</title>
        <author>
            <name>DH Network</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com/about.html"/>
        <id>https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com/about.html</id>

        <updated>2019-07-29T10:22:00-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    The purpose of the Digital Humanitarian Network (DHN) is to leverage digital volunteers in support&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>The purpose of the Digital Humanitarian Network (DHN) is to leverage digital volunteers in support of 21st century humanitarian response. More specifically, the aim of this <strong>network-of-networks</strong> is to form a consortium of Volunteer &amp; Technical Communities (V&amp;TCs) and to provide an interface between formal, professional humanitarian organizations and informal yet skilled-and-agile volunteer &amp; technical networks. Services offered by members of the DHNetwork are listedin the <a href="http://digitalhumanitarians.com/resource/dhn-catalogue" target="_self">DHN Catalogue</a>. We are taking an iterative approach in developing this interface and will expand membership to this network over time. <span style="text-decoration: underline;">Membership is by organization only</span>. </p>
<p>The purpose of the <a href="http://digitalhumanitarians.com/team-member-type/dhn-coordinator" target="_self">DHN Coordinators</a> is to review activation-requests and rapidly liaise with the different volunteer &amp; technical teams who are members of the DHN to build a Solution Team best able to act on a request. The Coordinators aim to provide a response to every request within 24 hours. </p>
<p>Please use #Digihums when tweeting about this network, thank you.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dg0pnhpu0">Contact</h2>
<p>Any inquiries can be made to <a href="mailto:contact@digitalhumanitarians.com" class="external embeddable" title="mailto:contact@digitalhumanitarians.com">contact@digitalhumanitarians.com</a>.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dgv1a4os0" class="title">DHN Co-Founders</h2>
<div id="node-team-full-group-right" class=" group-right field-group-div">
<div class="field field-name-field-name field-type-name field-label-hidden">
<div class="field-items">
<div class="field-item even"><img class="post__image" src="https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com/media/posts/2/andr.jpg" alt="" width="220" height="220"></div>
<div class="field-item even"><strong>Andrej Verity</strong></div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="field field-name-field-team-member-type field-type-taxonomy-term-reference field-label-hidden"> </div>
<div class="field field-name-field-team-title field-type-text field-label-hidden">
<div class="field-items">
<div class="field-item even">UN Office for the Coordination of Humanitarian Affairs</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="field field-name-field-email field-type-email field-label-hidden">
<div class="field-items">
<div class="field-item even"><a href="mailto:verity@un.org">verity@un.org</a></div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="field field-name-field-team-bio field-type-text-long field-label-hidden">
<div class="field-items">
<div class="field-item even">
<p>Andrej Verity is an information management officer at the United Nations (UN) Office for the Coordination of Humanitarian Affairs (OCHA) in New York and a co-founder of the Digital Humanitarian Network. Between responding to emergencies, he leads OCHA's multi-skilled Digital Services team providing strategic end-to-end service development, integrating and promoting standards and taxonomies, and managing platform-as-a-service support to a variety of sites ranging from ReliefWeb to the Humanitarian Data Exchange to the Financial Tracking Service to unocha.org. Verity has been working in the information management field for over 15 years, with the last 12 in the humanitarian realm. He has responded to many of the recent, major sudden onset emergencies - the 2010 Haiti earthquake, the 2010 Pakistan floods, the 2013-14 Philippines typhoon and the 2015 Nepal earthquake. Throughout the year, he spends time reflecting on his experiences and authoring forward-looking community papers such as the recent Blockchain for the Humanitarian Sector: Future opportunities (Dec 2016). Andrej openly shares his ideas in hopes to find energetic collaborative partners to help move the humanitarian community forward.</p>
<p> <img class="post__image" src="https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com/media/posts/2/drpat.jpg" alt="" width="220" height="220"></p>
<div id="node-team-full-group-right" class=" group-right field-group-div">
<div class="field field-name-field-name field-type-name field-label-hidden">
<div class="field-items">
<div class="field-item even"><strong>Dr. Patrick Meier</strong></div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="field field-name-field-team-member-type field-type-taxonomy-term-reference field-label-hidden"> </div>
<div class="field field-name-field-email field-type-email field-label-hidden">
<div class="field-items">
<div class="field-item even"><a href="mailto:patrick@irevolution.net">patrick@irevolution.net</a></div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="field field-name-field-team-bio field-type-text-long field-label-hidden">
<div class="field-items">
<div class="field-item even">
<p>Patrick is the co-founder of the Digital Humanitarian Network (DHN) and the author of the book "Digital Humanitarians." His influential blog, <a href="http://www.iRevolution.net">iRevolution.net</a> has received 2 million hits. Patrick presently serves as Co-Founder and Executive Director of WeRobotics. Previously, he served as Director of Social Innovation at QCRI, co-directed Harvard's Program on Crisis Mapping &amp; Early Warning and served as Director of Crisis Mapping at Ushahidi. Patrick is also a UNICEF Humanitarian Innovation Fellow and a Rockefeller Foundation &amp; PopTech Fellow. He holds holds a PhD from the Fletcher School and a Pre-Doctoral Fellowship from Stanford. He was born &amp; raised in Africa. Follow Patrick on Twitter at: <a href="https://twitter.com/PatrickMeier">patrickmeier</a>.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Cybersecurity and Humanitarian Organizations - On a Collision Course?</title>
        <author>
            <name>DH Network</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com/cybersecurity-and-humanitarian-organizations-on-a-collision-course.html"/>
        <id>https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com/cybersecurity-and-humanitarian-organizations-on-a-collision-course.html</id>

        <updated>2019-07-24T11:37:15-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com/media/posts/6/cybersecurity-august2018.png" alt="" />
                    Written by Emma Amaral View PDF File
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com/media/posts/6/cybersecurity-august2018.png" alt="" />
                <p><a href="https://app.box.com/s/8d8iyqxe0083fp3o4xsqj87pb3c30cb0?,&amp;source=aw&amp;utm_medium=affiliate&amp;utm_source=AWIN&amp;utm_theme=AlwaysOnDigital&amp;id=7010e000001LP9U&amp;utm_campaign=85386&amp;utm_content=0" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"></a>Written by <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/emma-m-amaral/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Emma Amaral</a></p>
<p> </p>
<a class="pdf-button" href="https://app.box.com/s/8d8iyqxe0083fp3o4xsqj87pb3c30cb0?,&amp;source=aw&amp;utm_medium=affiliate&amp;utm_source=AWIN&amp;utm_theme=AlwaysOnDigital&amp;id=7010e000001LP9U&amp;utm_campaign=85386&amp;utm_content=0" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">View PDF File</a>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Fostering the Right Workspace - Strategic Considerations for the Humanitarian Sector</title>
        <author>
            <name>DH Network</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com/fostering-right-workspace.html"/>
        <id>https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com/fostering-right-workspace.html</id>

        <updated>2019-07-24T11:37:09-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com/media/posts/7/fostering-workplace.png" alt="Fostering the Right Workspace" />
                    Written by Emma Amaral View PDF File
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com/media/posts/7/fostering-workplace.png" alt="Fostering the Right Workspace" />
                <p><a href="https://app.box.com/s/rky2y85zajh7v0vez5hr4l0d8oz1z04w?,&amp;source=aw&amp;utm_medium=affiliate&amp;utm_source=AWIN&amp;utm_theme=AlwaysOnDigital&amp;id=7010e000001LP9U&amp;utm_campaign=85386&amp;utm_content=0" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"></a>Written by <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/emma-m-amaral/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Emma Amaral</a></p>
<p> </p>
<a class="pdf-button" href="https://app.box.com/s/rky2y85zajh7v0vez5hr4l0d8oz1z04w?,&amp;source=aw&amp;utm_medium=affiliate&amp;utm_source=AWIN&amp;utm_theme=AlwaysOnDigital&amp;id=7010e000001LP9U&amp;utm_campaign=85386&amp;utm_content=0" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">View PDF File</a>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Community Content - JUMP Guides for Surveys</title>
        <author>
            <name>DH Network</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com/jump-guides-surveys.html"/>
        <id>https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com/jump-guides-surveys.html</id>

        <updated>2019-07-24T11:38:53-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com/media/posts/24/Screen-Shot-2019-07-23-at-4.04.52-PM.png" alt="" />
                    These documents were drafted independent of the Digital Humanitarian Network. They are hosted on our website&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com/media/posts/24/Screen-Shot-2019-07-23-at-4.04.52-PM.png" alt="" />
                <p id="mcetoc_1dgg84kkq6">These documents were drafted independent of the Digital Humanitarian Network. They are hosted on our website for the purpose of sharing with the community.</p>
<div style="display: grid; grid-column-gap: calc(.77143rem + .5vw);">
<div class="cat__item" style="border: 1px solid lightgrey;">
<div class="cat-item-img"><a href="https://app.box.com/s/lwwz8b157c6tndibdz6xvlykgr6qnqhb" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"> <img class="post__image" src="https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com/media/posts/24/Screen-Shot-2019-07-23-at-4.43.33-PM.png" alt="" width="100%" height="100%"> </a></div>
<div class="cat-item-label"><a href="https://app.box.com/s/lwwz8b157c6tndibdz6xvlykgr6qnqhb" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">JUMP Guides for Surveys: Data Collection</a></div>
</div>
<div class="cat__item" style="border: 1px solid lightgrey;">
<div class="cat-item-img"><a href="https://app.box.com/s/23lrm0d3st5gwqrbhwv0x2u9igfv044p" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><img class="post__image" src="https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com/media/posts/24/Screen-Shot-2019-07-23-at-4.19.16-PM.png" alt="" width="100%" height="100%"></a></div>
<div class="cat-item-label"><a href="https://app.box.com/s/23lrm0d3st5gwqrbhwv0x2u9igfv044p" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">JUMP Guides for Surveys: Data Privacy, Integrity and Security</a></div>
</div>
<div class="cat__item" style="border: 1px solid lightgrey;">
<div class="cat-item-img"><a href="https://app.box.com/s/8lgkls1zqj22qoynaydzycqv4xcmwzax" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><img class="post__image" src="https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com/media/posts/24/Screen-Shot-2019-07-23-at-4.04.52-PM.png" alt="" width="100%" height="100%"></a></div>
<div class="cat-item-label"><a href="https://app.box.com/s/8lgkls1zqj22qoynaydzycqv4xcmwzax" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">JUMP Guides for Surveys: Approach Your Audience</a></div>
</div>
<div class="cat__item" style="border: 1px solid lightgrey;">
<div class="cat-item-img"><a href="https://app.box.com/s/mnoqkhuxssv8vtppaypjezh207klok15" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><img class="post__image" src="https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com/media/posts/24/Screen-Shot-2019-07-23-at-4.20.51-PM.png" alt="" width="100%" height="100%"></a></div>
<div class="cat-item-label"><a href="https://app.box.com/s/mnoqkhuxssv8vtppaypjezh207klok15" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Design for Validity </a></div>
</div>
<div class="cat__item" style="border: 1px solid lightgrey;">
<div class="cat-item-img"><a href="https://app.box.com/s/elm7vp6eti8f2mf066wtdc8rtn24odp7" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><img class="post__image" src="https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com/media/posts/24/Screen-Shot-2019-07-23-at-4.23.06-PM.png" alt="" width="100%" height="100%"></a></div>
<div class="cat-item-label"><a href="https://app.box.com/s/elm7vp6eti8f2mf066wtdc8rtn24odp7" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">JUMP Guides for Surveys: Data Analysis</a></div>
</div>
</div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Data Protection in the Humanitarian Sector - A Blockchain Approach</title>
        <author>
            <name>DH Network</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com/blockchain-approach.html"/>
        <id>https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com/blockchain-approach.html</id>

        <updated>2019-07-24T11:37:02-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com/media/posts/8/blockchainapproach.png" alt="Data Protection in the Humanitarian Sector - A Blockchain Approach" />
                    Written by Irene Solaiman and Andrej Verity View PDF File
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://static.digitalhumanitarians.com/media/posts/8/blockchainapproach.png" alt="Data Protection in the Humanitarian Sector - A Blockchain Approach" />
                <p id="mcetoc_1dg0dfs1q0"><a href="https://app.box.com/s/blaoqt4pvmcb7kpcxgileqg412jpgxbn?,&amp;source=aw&amp;utm_medium=affiliate&amp;utm_source=AWIN&amp;utm_theme=AlwaysOnDigital&amp;id=7010e000001LP9U&amp;utm_campaign=85386&amp;utm_content=0" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"></a>Written by <a href="mailto:irs623@student.hks.harvard.edu" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Irene Solaiman</a> and <a href="mailto:verity@un.org">Andrej Verity</a></p>
<p> </p>
<a class="pdf-button" href="https://app.box.com/s/blaoqt4pvmcb7kpcxgileqg412jpgxbn?,&amp;source=aw&amp;utm_medium=affiliate&amp;utm_source=AWIN&amp;utm_theme=AlwaysOnDigital&amp;id=7010e000001LP9U&amp;utm_campaign=85386&amp;utm_content=0" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">View PDF File</a>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
